I know your song is always in your heart - 'Sin's Power'.
Can we rise up and sing?
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus rose I rose
When He rose we rose
Sin's power over us is broken
Sin's power over me is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went I went
Sin's power over us is broken
That is your secret.
Sin's power - you know what sin brings.
When you say, "Sin's power over me", it means tribulation, affliction, setback -
just mention any foolish thing - broken!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You must mean it when you sing it.
This is what you should sing before sleeping.
And when you are going, this should be in your heart.
Meditation.
As you are looking at me, that song should be going on in your heart.
It should go on in your heart.
It is well anointed to secure you for the glory.
You may be seated. Thank you.
Hallelujah.
If God's Word finds its place in your heart, let me see your joy.
That is why we are here; that is the most important thing -
God's Word must find its place in your heart.
God's Word in your heart heals, blesses, saves, brings Jesus to the scene.
Tell your neighbour, "God's Word in my heart".
I can't hear you.
[God's Word in my heart.]
Again and again.
Listen to that word 'heart' because Christianity lies in the heart.
Heart - the real man, the man himself.
Tell your neighbour, "Heart".
I can't hear you.
[Heart.]
Face your neighbour.
Heart - the real man, the man himself.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Inner my heart
Lord I want to be like Jesus
Listen to that.
Inner my heart
Not, "Lord I want to be like Jesus in my face".
Your face can be oblong or round; that is not an issue.
You must be like Jesus in your heart.
That is why faith is of man's heart because only faith pleases God.
See what you have been doing since morning.
Prayer is a work of faith; fasting is a work of faith.
Humility is a work of faith; faithfulness is a work of faith.
Kindness is a work of faith; obedience is a work of faith.
Only faith pleases God.
The real man - the man himself.
If I'm talking to you and not your heart, I'm not talking to you.
When you are talking to me not from your heart, I will not be able to help you.
If what you are saying is not from your heart, I will not be able to help you.
I'm a man of heart; I must talk to the man of heart.
Heart! Heart!
Heart to heart!
Are you here - your heart, your real man?
Ask your neighbour, "Are you here - your heart?"
I can't hear you.
[Are you here - your heart?]
Our presence here today is all about identification -
to identify and acknowledge our weakness.
To identify and acknowledge our weakness is victory itself.
You say, "Ah, I'm here because I'm a smoker".
"I'm here because I'm a liar."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
"I'm here because I'm a thief."
To identify and acknowledge your weakness is victory itself.
Take note - it is 50 percent of the victory.
"I'm a smoker; I don't want to smoke any longer.
Jesus, help me. That is why I'm here.
I don't want to smoke any longer."
It is 50 percent of the victory; the remaining 50 percent, leave it for God.
Right now, begin to identify where you need to improve.
Ask your neighbour, "Where do you need to improve?"
Whatever blessing you have received in terms of miracle or healing cannot be permanent;
it is our weakness that robs us.
That is what satan will use to take away the blessing you have received.
That weakness is the route satan will take to snatch away the blessing you have received.
Ask your neighbour, "Where do you need to improve?"
Ask your neighbour again.
[Where do you need to improve?]
I can't hear you.
Ask your neighbour.
[Where do you need to improve?]
Where do you need to improve in order to have a permanent miracle, a miracle forever?
If not, your life will continue to be epileptic - up, down.
Yesterday, you were once rich; today, you are on the street.
Yesterday, you were once healthy; today, you are very sick.
Satan uses our weakness as a route to get us, to snatch the one we have from God.
You know what it means: when you were alright yesterday and today is the opposite.
You lived at peace yesterday; but today - opposite.
You know what it means.
There is a song you sing.
It shall be permanent
What the Lord has done for me
No, it cannot be permanent if you don't block that weakness - the route satan uses to get to you.
He uses that route to get to you - the route, your weakness.
It is the route, road satan uses to get to you.
Identify where you need to grow, where you need to improve.
TT: Mel Flowers 13/04/2019